挨饿游戏
嗨 凯迷思！
Hey, Kantmiss!
我的伟大 和强大的
I am the great
and powerful--
啊哈！
Aah!
戴尔！
Dale!
只是想 给你个惊喜
Just wanted
to surprise you.
你让我错失了我的猎物
You made me miss my shot.
嗷
Ow.
狗杂种！
我的背啊！
Son of a bitch!
My back!
看看我得到了什么
Look what I got.
那玩意是真的吗？
Is it real?
哦！
想想看！
Ohh!
Psych!
是块令人作呕的面包！
It's gag bread!
看着你
Look at you.
好吧
Right.
你知道...
You know...
我们可以离开这里
we could run away
from here.
我们可以找到别的地方住
We could live
someplace else.
像在哪里？
Like where?
任何地方 只要比这地方好就行
Anywhere that's
better than here.
达尔富尔 叙利亚
Darfur. Syria.
纽泽西州
New Jersey.
戴尔 那真的很浪漫并且...
Dale, that's--that's
romantic and all...
但我没办法离开我的妹妹
but I can't leave
my sister.
我也不能离开
I can't leave either.
亲爱的年老奶奶等着我照顾她
My dear, old grandma
depends on me to feed her.
天啊 我永远没有我自己的孩子
God, I am never
having kids.
我的意思是你如何养育一个孩子
I mean, how can
you raise a child
在这一个他监看着的地方
in a world
where they televise
人间各种悲剧 然后转眼忘记
all of life's misery and
inhumanity and then pass it off
最为变态的一种娱乐
as some sort of twisted
entertainment?
“挨饿游戏”
"The Hunger Games."
成年礼和怀孕
"16 and Pregnant."
早安
Good morning,
十二区的饥饿公民们
hungry citizens
of District 12.
今天的新闻是 我们仍然没有食物
In today's news,
we still have no food,
天气跟大便一样糟
and the weather
will be shitty.
哦 还有别忘了
Oh, and don't forget,
今天是抽签仪式
today is
the Gathering Ceremony,
因此各位家长请把你们心爱的孩子带来
so, parents, please bring
your beloved children
广场 来一次死亡乐透
to the square
for a random death lottery.
谢谢
Thank you.
我听说有些孩子 太害怕
I heard that some kids
are so afraid
被选上
of getting picked
for the Games
所以试着采取一些丧失资格的手段
that they'll actually
try to get disqualified
造成伤害或自残
by injuring or
maiming themselves.
那只是个传说吧
That's an urban legend.
呃！
Uhh!
排好队
Get in line.
哦 别这样
贱人
Oh, come on,
bitch.
因此事实
Ipso facto p--
你的行动特权 已经没有了
Your movie franchise
is over.
回去排队
Get back in line.
嗜血的家伙
Bloody dick.
哎 别说话
Hey, no talking.
继续前进
Keep it moving.
我得去找我的妹妹
I gotta find my sister.
祝你好运
Good luck.
佩图妮
凯迷思
Petunia.
Kantmiss.
嘿 老妈
Hey, Mom.
我好害怕 凯迷思 人家怕怕
I'm scared, Kantmiss.
I'm scared.
嘿 嘿 不要怕 我给你带来这个
Hey, hey, don't be.
I got you this.
这是最勇敢的鸟 上面还有...
It's the most courageous bird
that there is...
一只鸡
a chicken.
当你带着它
没什么不好的事会发生在你身上
When you wear this,
nothing bad can happen to you.
嘘嘘
不 不要哭了
Shh. Shh.
No, don't cry.
你会没事的 好吗
You're gonna
be fine, okay?
我保证
I promise.
继续前进
Keep moving.
排好队！
Line up!
男左女右！
Girls on the right.
Boys on the left!
欢迎来到第75届 挨饿游戏
Welcome to the 75th annual
Starving Games.
哦 哦！哦！
Oh. Oh! Ohh!
嘿 哦！
Hey.
Ohh!
那是 我的香肠！
But that was my sausage!
从我们尊敬的领袖传来一段视讯
And now a video
from our esteemed leader,
雪球总统
President Snowballs.
他曾经杀死他的老母......
He once killed
his own mother...
因为她忘了切掉三明治外面面包的皮
because she forgot to cut
the crust off his PB&J.
他唯一的脸书好朋友
是梅尔·吉布逊
His only Facebook friend
is Mel Gibson.
他有一个自己的部落格
He has an online blog
在上面泄漏电影的结局
that gives away
the endings of movies
上面没有声明 “狗仔警告 ”
without ever using the
disclaimer "spoiler alert."
什么
他就是...
What?
He is...
世界上最可怕的人
the most terrible man
in the world.
我不是很喜欢啤酒的
I don't always like beer,
但是如果我想要
我选择特雷斯·一块死
but when I want one,
I choose Tres Equis.
味道有点像尿一样
Tastes like piss water.
啊哈！
Aah!
每一年 我都会让你们观看此视讯
Every year, I make you
watch this video,
因为 你都是傻瓜
because, well,
you're dumb.
人们忘记在过去
People forget
how in the past
狗屎真的击中了风扇
shit really hit the fan.
组织太大了
并且人们开始失去信心
Corporations got too big,
and people lost trust.
他们静坐罢工 聚众闹事
They staged sit-ins.
They rioted.
你选出女神卡卡作为总统
You elected Lady Gaga
as President
和她的竞选搭档 妮奇·米娜
and her running mate
Nicki Minaj.
这就是为什么我们穿
这些稀奇古怪的衣服吧
That's why we wear
these kooky clothes now
和怪异的发型
and have bizarre hairdos.
后来我接手
Then I took over
把国家分成各区域
and separated the country
into districts
所以那些愚蠢的行为
永远不会再发生
so that stupid shit
never happened again.
啊哈！
Aah!
已经证明 民主没有用
You've proven that democracy
doesn't work,
在这里以我的第六感来看
and I'm here, in my sixth
self-proclaimed term,
保证所有的自由意志都不见
to ensure that all free will
is expunged,
别再把那丑陋的头像放上去
never to rear
its ugly head again.
是的 自从那后导致我们今天的情况
Yes, that brings us to today.
只是为了证明我是一个很屌的人
Just to prove what
a sick, sadistic prick I am
你们是如此无能为力
and how you have
no control...
自从看过 阿诺的“过关斩将”
and admittedly after
watching "The Running Man"
和日本变态片“大逃杀”
and the Japanese
cult hit "Battle Royale,"
我想出了 挨饿游戏
I came up with
the Starving Games.
从各地区挑选两个孩子
Two kids from each district
are selected
玩死亡游戏 只有一个幸存者
to play a game to the death
with only one survivor.
赢家能获得丰富奖金
The winner is to be
showered with a bounty,
包括一只老火腿...
including an old ham...
哦 我超爱老火腿
Oh, I love old ham.
凭此券到地铁速食店
this coupon to Subway--
购买任何东西可以打六折
buy any foot-long
for a six-inch price--
和...
and...
一个被吃过一部份的酸黄瓜
a partially eaten pickle.
最后祝玩 挨饿游戏愉快
So happy Starving Games,
祝你永远好运
and may the odds be
never in your favor.
雪球总统出品
A President Snowballs
production.
现在开始选出参加者！咳咳
Now let the gathering
begin! Ahem.
休·杰那斯
Hugh Janus.
嗯
Hmm?
不在吗 嗯 好的
No? Yeah. All right.
我再重抽一个 嘿
I'll pick again. Heh.
菲尔·穆特思(谐音似塞满女性器官)
Phil Mahooters.
请上来菲尔·穆特思
Please, Phil Mahooters?
狄恩·格布瑞(音似性无能)
Dean Gullberry.
看看身后
Everyone look around.
四处找一下 狄恩·格布瑞
Check behind you
for a Dean Gullberry.
这是全国直播！
This is being televised
around the country!
你们不要笑的太早
You won't be laughing
当你们当中两个被抽出并丢进屠宰场
when two of you are picked
and thrown into the arena
你就隔屁了
for your
most certain deaths.
咳咳
Ahem.
没关系
It's okay.
佩图妮·艾薇秀逗
Petunia Evershot.
好喔！
Whoo!
太棒！太棒！
Yes! Yes!
老娘没抽到
I didn't get picked.
好喔！
Hoo-whoo!
呼！喔！呀！
Hoo! Whoo! Yeah!
我没抽到
♪ I didn't get picked ♪
我已年满18岁
♪ I'm 18 now
对我来说不用再游戏
♪ No mo' games for me now ♪
呜 认命吧
♪ Unh, unh, suck it ♪
喔！来吧！
给我来个
Whoo! Come on!
Gimme some.
嗯 再来一次
哦！噢
Yeah. One more.
Oh! Whew.
但是我被选中
But I got picked.
佩图妮 我很抱歉
Petunia, I am so sorry.
佩图妮 不 这不公平
Petunia, no. Not fair.
不要给我可怜小狗的眼神
Do not give me
those puppy-dog eyes.
我自愿！
I volunteer!
哦
Oh.
我自愿参加挨饿游戏！
I volunteer
for the Starving Games!
谢谢 我的大姐姐啊
Thanks, big sis.
哦！如果你不能活着回来
Oh! If you never make it
back from the Games,
我可以吃掉您的宠物仓鼠吗？
can I eat
your pet hamster？
什么
What?
来吧 亲爱的
Come, dear.
现在 让我们挑一个男孩加入你的队伍
Now let's pick a boy to
join you in the games.
我也自愿！
I volunteer also!
谁说的
Who said that?
是我
I did.
我是彼得·马拉鸡
I'm Peter Malarkey.
哦
Oh.
嘿 凯迷思
Hey, Kantmiss.
我自告奋勇 因为我喜欢你
I volunteered
because I like you,
非常喜欢 我很抱歉
a lot, and I--
I'm sorry.
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
嗯......
Um...
我 我是面包师的儿子
I'm--I'm the baker's son.
有一次 你饿的时候我给你面包
I once fed you
when you were hungry.
哦 我想起
Oh, right.
你给我一个核桃面包
You gave me
that walnut bread.
嗯
Yeah.
对啊
老娘对坚果严重过敏
I have a severe
nut allergy,
我差点死了
and I almost died.
让我们的参赛者发言！
Let's hear it for
our contestants!
而且不要忘了转台看 挨饿游戏
And don't forget to tune in
to the Starving Games
唐顿修道院 影集终后就是
after the season finale
of "Downton Abbey."
我们不能说再见吗
Can't we say
our goodbyes?
当然可以 亲爱的
Of course, dear.
中央政府还是有点人性的
The Capital isn't
completely inhumane.
你有9秒的时间
You got 9 seconds.
佩图妮！ 凯迷思！
Petunia!
Kantmiss!
不要担心 你跟妈妈在一起就可以放心了
Don't worry. You're in
good hands with Mom.
不知彼得到底在想什么
What's up with
that Peter dude?
什么
What?
我的意思是 他像一个白痴对不对
I mean he's
a total dork, right?
你觉得他能帮什么忙吗
How much do you
think he benches?
呃......
Uh...
时间到了！
Time's up!
戴尔！ 是吗
Dale!
Yeah?
答应我 你会照顾佩图妮！
Promise me you'll
take care of Petunia!
我会的 凯迷思
I will,
Kantmiss.
我保证
I promise.
等一下！
Wait!
待会见
Later.
脑残
Shitheads.
耐吉的标志
The Nike Swoosh?
是的 我开始在
Yes, I started selling
我的脸上卖广告空间
advertising space
on my face.
你愿意卖自己 跟妓女一样
Your willingness to sell
out and whore yourself
是我让你当上头不程式员的主要因素
is the primary reason I
made you head programmer.
谢谢你 总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
我们的大电视节目秀怎样了
How is
the big TV show looking?
太棒了 阿什顿·库奇取代查理辛
Fantastic. We've replaced Charlie
Sheen with Ashton Kutcher,
没有人在意给份狗屎的
and no one really
seems to give a shit.
挨饿游戏
And the Starving Games?
那将是一个超棒的演出
It's gonna be
a great show.
我们有一些 非常有趣的参赛者
We have some
very interesting contestants,
12区有2名自愿者
with 2 volunteers
from District 12.
自愿者
Volunteers.
笑得我尿失禁
R-O-T-F-L-O-L.
因为你把它制订成法律
And because
you made it law
说如果有谁不看竞赛的话会被公开打鞭
that whoever doesn't watch the
Games would be publicly flogged,
我们期待 创高收视率
we're expecting
record high ratings.
经过去年的当机
Well, after
last years debacle,
我真的别无选择
I really had no choice.
名人一起挨饿游戏 是一个很烂的主意
"Celebrity Starving
Games" was a lousy idea.
没有人会参加的
No one
could have anticipated
因为欧普拉会吃掉其他选手
that Oprah would eat
all the other contestants.
我希望这个游戏结束能功德圆满
I want this game to go
off without a hitch.
我不想 有一些败笔
I don't want
some underdog
从一个贫穷的地区 参加游戏 并煽动群众
from a poor district to enter the
Games and stir up the masses
她的射箭技能 和她的黑色的头发
with her archery skills
and her brunette hair
辫子塑造成一个注册商标
fashioned into a
trademark single braid,
鼓舞人心的反抗 不仅将颠覆我的统治
inspiring revolt which will not
only overthrows my presidency,
同样也产生一个成功的
but also spawns
a successful
重量级的反动炸弹
four-quadrant
blockbuster.
哦！
Ohh!
我可能需要 一个新的园丁
And I may need
a new gardener.
我是尸躺立·西舍曼 这里是
I'm Stanley Ceaserman,
and this is
挨饿游戏 前秀 !
"The Starving Games
Countdown Show!"
明天 游戏就要开始
Tomorrow, the Games begin,
但今晚 我们要与参赛者会面
but tonight, we're going
to meet the contestants.
你会一个个认识他们
You'll get to know them
听听背后感人的故事
through their
touching backstories,
我们会使用大量编辑过的
where we'll manipulate you
with heavily edited
家庭录影带 悲惨的见证来感动你们
home video footage
and tragic testimonials.
当你们开始对他们有所感动
Then, when you're emotionally
attached to them,
我们会把他们送去恐怖的大屠杀
we'll send them off
to their horrific slaughter.
让我们见一下我们第一个参赛者
Let's meet
our first contestant.
按照区域从第一个区开始
Going in order
from District One,
他很有希望能赢得这场比赛
he's the odds-on favorite
to win this thing.
他是金发细腰的
He's blond. He's Waspy.
他是年轻的雅利安人的化身
He's the Aryan youth incarnate.
他就是马哥！
He's Marco!
呀！
Yeah!
啊啊！呀！
Ahh! Yeah!
你好 帅哥
Hello, guy.
和我们谈谈你自己
Tell us
about yourself.
我来自一区
这是一个主要的区
I'm from District One.
It's a prime district.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是辛纳蒙
I'm Cinnamon,
你的发型师
your stylist.
你还行吗
How are you holding up?
我很害怕
I'm scared.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
啊 我来告诉你
Ahh. I'm here
to tell you
我相信你
that I
believe in you.
你能赢
You can win this.
我看过你的记录
I looked
at your records,
你比他们都要聪明和狡猾
and you are smarter and
craftier than all of them.
真的吗你觉得 我会赢吗
Really? You think
that I can win?
是的 帕特丽夏
Yes, Patricia.
我就知道
I know it.
谁是帕特丽夏
Who's Patricia?
你不是从三区来的女孩
You're not the girl
from District Three?
不 我来至十二区
No, I'm from
District 12.
你知道 这完全正常的
You know, this is
perfectly normal.
你看起来很坚强
You seem like you strong--
现在从12区来的彼得 马拉鸡
And now, from District 12,
Peter Malarkey.
彼得和我们聊一聊
So, Peter, tell us,
在你生命中有没有比较特别的人呢
is there a special
someone in your life?
嗯
Yeah.
是有一个
Yeah, there is someone.
是啊 跟我们说说
Aww.
哦
Ohh.
好吧 告诉我们
Well, do tell.
那人也在现场
The person's
actually here tonight,
那人同样...
a person who is...
也在游戏里吗
also in the Games.
在游戏跟你再一起吗
In the Games with you?
噢哇 噢哇
Aww.
那继续
Well, go on.
怎么讲......
Well...
它是我一直在等候的人
it's a person
I've been wanting
可以多相处的
to get closer to
for a long time.
你这狗杂种
You son of a bitch.
所以...
So...
身材高大
tall,
美丽的大眼睛
with beautiful eyes
身材火辣的冒烟 但是......
and a smoking
hot bod, but...
你知道吗 比什么都重要的是
you know,
more than anything,
这个人有很多的爱心
this person's
got a lot of heart.
噢哇 噢哇
Aww.
好吧 你一定要告诉我们是谁呢
Well, you must tell us.
Who is it?
他就是马哥！
It's Marco!
我吗
Me?
嘿
Heh.
咦 咦
Huh?
让我们以掌声谢谢彼得
Let's hear it
for Peter.
你这个小混蛋！
You little shit!
我会一脚踩爆你的小菊花！
I'm gonna stick
a foot in your ass!
哦！哎呀
Ohh! Jeez.
你说的是怎么一回事呢
What the hell
was that about?
这就是所谓的 建立联盟
It's called
building an alliance.
你没看过“幸存者” 或“老大哥”
Haven't you ever watched
"Survivor" or "Big Brother"?
啊哈！ 什么
Aah!
When's--
你最近什么时候修剪你的脚趾甲
When was the last time
you trimmed your toenails?
哦
Ohh.
现在请我们最后的参赛者
And now, for our
final contestant,
从十二区来的
from District 12,
凯迷思·艾薇秀逗
Kantmiss Evershot.
喔！
Whoo!
让我们来看看
Let's take a look.
凯迷思是世界上最好的大姐姐
Kantmiss is the best
big sister in the world.
她照顾我 她养我 给我衣服
She takes care of me.
She feeds me. She clothes me.
她读书给我听
She even reads to me.
自从爸爸去世后
Ever since Dad died,
妈妈变得神智不清
Mom's been
a little bummed out,
但是并不阻止 我们三个寻找快乐
but that doesn't stop the three of
us from having a whole lot of fun.
从第一次 我看到凯迷思 我就知道
From the first time
I saw Kantmiss, I knew.
我就知道她是我生命中的那个人
I knew she was
the one for me.
她不得了
She's got class.
她是一个真正的淑女
She's a real lady.
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
哦！ 哦 我的天啊
Ohh!
Oh, my God.
哦！ 哦！
Ohh!
是不是 刚刚很感人
Isn't that
just touching?
噢哇 噢哇
Aww.
让我们请她出来好吗
Let's bring her out,
shall we?
凯迷思·艾薇秀逗！
Kantmiss Evershot!
凯迷思 这礼服真是漂亮
So, Kantmiss,
that's quite a dress.
给我们一点旋转
Give us a little spin.
嘿 继续
Heh. Go on.
不要害羞
Don't be shy.
非常好
Very nice.
哦
Oh.
哇 我听懂了是点火
Wow, I'm getting word
that flames
旋转礼服会烧起来
actually ignite
from the dress.
火焰
Flames?
哦！ ！哦！
Oh! Oh!
哦 我的天啊 哦
Oh, my God.
Oh.
哦 啊哈！
Oh, Aah!
你们为什么还在鼓掌 你们这些笨蛋
Why are you clapping,
you stupid?!
啊哈！
Aah!
我烧起来了！ 我烧起来了！
I'm on fire!
让我们谢谢凯迷思 火焰的女孩！
Let's hear it for Kantmiss,
the girl on fire!
啊 ！ 着火了！
Ah!
It's on fire!
着火了！它烧起来了！
It's on fire! It burns!
我烧起来了！
I'm on fire!
早安 体育粉丝们
Good morning, sport fans,
欢迎来到75届 挨饿游戏
and welcome to the 75th
annual Starving Games.
我是主持人鲍伯·嗨洛克
I'm your host Bob Hylox,
与我的搭档
and with me is my sidekick
毒舌评论员 克利弗·威廉姆斯(大砍刀)
and color commentator,
Cleaver Williams.
砍刀 你好
Cleaver, how you doing?
今天的比赛感到兴奋吗
Excited about
today's Games?
太棒了
Fantastic.
克利弗是过去游戏的赢家
Cleaver is a past
Games winner, of course.
事实上砍刀你为什么不告诉大家
In fact, Cleaver,
why don't you tell everybody
在各区观看得大家
in the district watching,
你是怎么得到 那可爱的的绰号
how you got
that delightful nickname.
我用砍刀 杀掉每一人
I used a meat cleaver
to kill everyone.
仍然宝刀未老
Still got the old moves.
你好 西丽
Hello, Siri.
你好 萨乐卡
Hello, Seleca.
最近好吗
How's it hanging, boo?
不怎好
Low and to the left.
不错
Good one.
好的 看来参赛者
All right.
Looks like the contestants
已经到现场了
have taken the field.
西丽 镜头切换到现场
All right, Siri,
cut to the field.
祷告吧 小子 因为你已经死了
Say your prayers, my son,
'cause you are dead.
倒数开始
And the countdown
has begun.
30,
29 ...
29...
哦 天啊 28 ...
Oh, God.
28...
27 ...
27...
嗯
Hmm?
26 ...
26...
25 ...
25...
24,
23,
21...
21 ...
现在这点是非常重要的
Now, it's very important
要求参赛者 不要动
that the contestants
don't move
数到零之前银圈不会关闭
off the silver circles
before zero.
否则会被蹦 蹦
Otherwise, kablammo,
场上装满炸药
as the field is booby-trapped
with explosives.
不需要提醒我
Don't need to remind me.
我偷跑太早 以至现在不能嗯嗯与拉拉
I went too soon, and I
still can't poop right.
看看示范
How 'bout that?
13,
12...
12 ...
11 ... 咦
11...Huh?
你们在这里干什么
What are you
doing here?
我们被邀请来的
We were asked
to perform
举行开幕仪式
at the opening
ceremony.
这就是屠宰场
This is the arena.
哦 你应该找第二现场
Oh, you're looking
for stage two.
哦 谢谢 谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
Thanks.
哎呀 不错
Oops.
哇！这是什么方法 开始游戏！
Wow! What a way
to start the Games!
10,
9...
9 ...
8...
8 ...
7...
7 ...
6,
5...
5 ...
4...
4 ...
3...
3 ...
2...
2 ...
1.
西丽 更血腥些
Siri, more blood.
哦
Oh.
这样好多
Much better.
哦！ 哦！
Ooh!
是马哥！呀！
Yeah, Marco! Yeah!
放手！
Let go!
我先来的！
I got here first!
啊！ 现在把它给我！
Yaah!
Now give it to me!
我不会轻易放手的
No. I'm not letting go.
你背后中镖！
There is a dagger
in your back!
我没事！
I'm okay!
什么
What?
没事
It's fine.
It's fine?
这样没事 你不放手
Seriously?
You're not letting go?
我要这个背包！
I want this backpack!
我要它 它是我的！
I want it. It's mine!
我不会轻易放手！
I'm not letting go!
那是我的背包！
That was my backpack!
那是什么声音
What was that sound?
大炮的声音 他们发射的
It's the cannon.
They shoot it off
每当有人死了 他们就发射一发
to announce whenever
someone is killed.
很好 看来我的胜算
Nice.
Looks like the odds
对我来说多一些
just got better
for me, then.
我的蛋蛋！
My balls!
哦！看来很痛
Oh! That has
got to hurt.
让我们来看看慢动作重播
Let's see
an instant replay.
我的蛋蛋！
My balls!
我的蛋蛋
My ball--
我的蛋蛋 我 我的蛋
My--My ball--
我的蛋
My ball--
我的蛋！
My balls!
这样会让我起笑 鲍伯
That makes me
laugh, Bob.
离我远点！
Get away from me!
哇！
Wow!
这个女孩是谁
Who is this girl?
她来自什么区
What district
is she from?
我站在杂碎的十二区
I'm standing here
in scummy District 12,
那里的人们 不敢相信 彼得和凯迷思的
where people can't believe
that Peter and Kantmiss
可以存活过开幕式
have actually survived
the opening.
你可以看到大家都兴奋高亢
You can see
the excitement is high,
很长一段时间这个区域都没有赢过
as no one from this district
has won in a very long time.
呀！ 啊！
Yeah!
Unh!
加油 凯迷思！喔！
Go, Kantmiss! Whoo!
这是我的马子！
That's my girl!
呀！
Yeah!
转回转播台
Back to you
in the studio.
我上电视了！
I'm on TV!
谢谢 尸躺立
Thanks, Stanley.
现在比数如何 砍刀
And how's the scoreboard
looking, Cleaver?
很多人已死
Got a lot
of people dead.
尽管如此 还有很多人活着
Still,
lot of people alive.
让我突然眼睛一亮
Enlightening.
哦 看来凯迷思的以他的方式
Oh, looks like Kantmiss
is making her way
来到屠宰场的边缘
to the outer edge
of the arena.
西丽 让她慢下来
Siri, slow her down.
噢
Ow.
现在 让我们的凯迷思 回到场中央
Now let's get Kantmiss back
to the center of the action.
呼啦！
Holla!
释放惊心动魄的音效
And cue the thrilling
action music.
哦
Ooh.
嗯
Hmm.
你想要玩玩那就来
Oh, you want to play, huh? Okay.
西丽
Siri.
耶 你需要什么
Yeah, what you need?
以最新的攻击她
Attack her
with the latest
用我们最先进武器
technological weaponry
we have.
喔 哈！
Whoo-hah!
噢 该死！
Oh, shit!
呀！嘻嘻！
Yah! Whee hee hee!
嘻嘻！
Hee hee hee!
不
No.
怎么怎么
What? What?
很高兴看到我柳丁吗
Orange you glad
to see me?
嘿 嘿 嘿！
Hey, hey, hey!
当你以一个黄色眼神你会得到什么
What do you get
when you cross an orange
昆汀 塔沦落(色情片导演)
with Quentin Tarantino?
“色情小说” 你会得到什么呢
"Pulp Fiction."
You get it?
果浆
Pulp.
嘿 凯迷思
Hey, Kantmiss,
我最后一次见到小笼包
last time I saw
tits that small,
是我看到一对金橘的时候
I was staring
at a pair of kumquats.
啊哈！
Aah!
加油 凯迷思！
Go, Kantmiss!
哦
Ooh,
她肯定会说 哟'对不起踢爆你屁股！
she sure showed
yo' sorry ass up!
你 你 闭嘴 西丽 你闭嘴！
You--You shut up, Siri.
You shut up!
妈的 不要恨 玩家
Shit. Don't hate
the player.
你 恨这游戏！
You--
Hate the game!
哇！我从来没有见过 有人这样做
Wow! I've never seen
anyone do that before.
她坏蛋
She's badass.
我顶
Respect.
让我想起了跟自己一点点像
Reminds me
a little bit of myself.
在我有过多的情绪前 我要停下来
I'll stop now before
I get too emotional.
尝尝老娘的屁！
Eat my ass!
你认为你很神勇吗
Think you're so tough?
看看你能不能搞定这 贱人！
Well, come back
from this, bitch!
嘿 朋友们 加油！
我们走这条路！
Hey, guys, come on!
Let's go this way!
来吧 快点！
Come on. Hurry!
走吧！
Let's go!
当我发现她的时候
她就是我的
When I see her,
she's mine.
她肯定在这里的某个地方
She's gotta be
around here somewhere.
你确定凯迷思 走这条路
You sure Kantmiss
came this way?
嗯 我知道
Uh, I know it.
你怎么能这么肯定
我们可以信任你吗
How can we be so sure
that we can trust you?
我的意思是
你是自愿参加这游戏的
I mean, didn't you volunteer
to be in the games
只是为了接近凯迷思的
just so you can get
closer to Kantmiss?
不
No.
我的意思是 也许一开始是
I mean, maybe at first,
但我不再喜欢她了
but I don't
like her anymore.
真的吗
Really?
嗯 你知道
Well, you know,
早在12区时
back in District 12,
she's--
她的作为相当是妓女
she's known
as quite the whore.
啊
Ahh.
她在那里
There.
嘿
Heh.
做得好 彼得
Nice work, Peter.
谢谢
Thanks.
我会打爆她的肠子
I'm gonna bust her gut
wide open.
这个小公主 全部是我的
This little princess
is all mine.
啊！
Raah!
凯迷思在那！
And there's Kantmiss!
哦 我们会杀了你
Oh, no.
We're gonna kill you.
在我们吃 我们的美味佳肴
Right after we eat
our delicious treats.
咦
Huh?
你怎么能 与他们搅和在一起
How can you
be with them?
我不知道
I don't know.
我...
I--I guess I just...
真的很喜欢他们
really like them.
它们太酷了 而广受欢迎
Th-They're so cool
and popular.
我的意思是
我是高中的艾薇俱乐部
I mean, I'm in
the high school A/V club.
我从来没有机会与痞子们一起玩
I've never been able to hang
with the in crowd before.
嗯
跟我们在一起
Mmm.
Stay with us.
太好了
So good.
嗯 哦
Mmm. Oh.
嘿 他们说 他们希望
跟我一起去舞会
Hey, they said they want
to go to prom with me.
我们要去租一辆豪华轿车
和一切东西
We're gonna rent a limo
and everything.
是不是真棒
Isn't that awesome?
彼得 它们只是利用你
Peter, they are
just using you.
在挨饿游戏只能有一个赢家
There can only be one winner
of the Starving Games.
好的
Right.
很好 凯迷思 游戏就要结束
All right, Kantmiss,
game over.
格老木 你上
Glammer, you're up.
喔呼呼！
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
哦！看样子这里有一个溜鸟侠
Oh! Looks like we got
ourselves a streaker.
每一场比赛都会发生
Happens every Game.
鬼叫 雅虎
What a yahoo.
快滚 贱人 快滚！
Get out of here, man.
Get out of here!
回来 回来
Come back here.
给我......
Give me that.
刺得好 嗯
Nice impaling.
Yeah.
他这样投
He did this.
然后 它这样回
Then it did that.
事实上 砍刀
Indeed, Cleaver.
今天绝对是
And that's
definitely gonna be
屠宰日！
our Kill of the Day!
Kill of the Day!
屠宰日 屠宰日！
Kill of the Day--
of the Day!
自由屠宰日
Our Kill of the Day
is brought to you
赌命保险赞助播出
by BetLife
insurance.
因为生命是宝贵的...
Because life
is precious...
赌命 赌命
BetLife.
我们要怎样玩死她
How are we going
to kill her?
咳咳
Ahem.
呃......
Uh...
为什么不要我们先离开
why don't
we just take off,
嗯 去杀死 其他一些孩子
uh, go kill
some other kids
稍后再回来吗
and come back later?
我们会等着你的
We'll wait.
她迟早会下来的
She has to come down
sooner or later.
太恶了
Gross.
嘿
Hey.
嘘
Shh.
哦
Oh.
有蜂巢砸在他们的头上
Have the bees
land on their heads.
好吧 嘘 嘘
Okay. No, shh. Shh.
这些都是守卫兵蜂
Those are tracker bees.
被叮到会产生严重的幻觉
Getting stung causes
serious hallucinations.
或隔屁
Or death.
哦！
Oh!
嗷！嗷！
Ow! Ow!
哦！我的屁股！啊！
Oh! My ass! Aah!
我想我刚刚吞下一只！
I think I
just swallowed one!
哇
Whoa.
哦
Ooh.
哇 哦
Whoa. Ooh.
什么
What--
哦 我的天哦！
Oh, my God. Oh!
哦 哦
Oh. Oh.
喔
Whoo.
哦
Oh.
不会吧
No way.
两道彩虹
Double rainbow.
呜！
Whoo!
两道彩虹！哈！
Double rainbow! Ha!
哦
Oh.
它开始看起来
It's starting to look
像四道彩虹！
like a quadruple rainbow!
哦 我的------天啊！
Oh, my Gooood!
没错！没错！
Yes! Yes!
啊哈哈！
Ah ha ha!
哦 彩虹的味道
Oh, taste the rainbow.
哦
Ooh.
哦 哦
Oh. Oh.
哦 哇
Oh. Wha?
哦 我的
Oh, my--
那是...
What is...
哦
Oh.
不要有突然的大动作
Do not make
any sudden movements.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我从来没有 看过这情况发生
I've never
seen this happen before.
它们是什么
What are they?
灵魂保护者
Soul keepers.
灵魂保护者！
Soul keepers!
啊！哦 我的天！ 搞定他们！
搞定他们！
Ah! Oh, my God! Get 'em off!
Get 'em off!
搞定他们！ 搞定他们！
你们别想 带走我的灵魂！
You are not
keeping my soul!
哦！为什么呢
Oh! Why?
你头顶有一个
Right above your head.
不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no.
噢
Whew.
我觉得 我全部搞定他们
I think
I got 'em all.
灵魂保护者持有 所有我们古老的祖先亡灵
Soul Keepers hold all of the
souls of our ancient ancestors.
那是我妹妹
There goes my sister,
我的奶奶
my grandma
和我喝醉的希拉阿姨
and my drunk
Aunt Sheila.
哎呀
Oops.
你是谁
Who are you?
我们是一个值得骄傲的古代人
We are a proud
and ancient people
由詹姆斯·卡麦隆创建
created by James Cameron.
我是世界之王！
I'm the king
of the world!
看这里
Here.
给我你的发辫
Give me your hair.
把尾端联结一起就可做爱
We'll join the ends
and make love,
纳美人的格调
Na'vi style.
好啊
Okay.
哦
Ohh.
嗯
Yeah.
哦 是的
Oh, yes.
凯迷思
Kantmiss.
凯迷思！
Kantmiss!
是
Yes.
凯迷思！ 凯迷思！
Kantmiss! Kantmiss!
凯迷思！
Kantmiss!
难道你想跟我交配
Are you trying
to hook up with me?
什么没有！
What? No!
不 不 不 不 嗯......
No, no, no, no. Um...
我认为我 只是产生幻觉
I think that I was
just hallucinating.
你最好不要 我只有12岁(未成年)
You better not be.
I'm only 12.
依我所见
如果我们要生存
The way I see it,
if we're gonna survive,
我们应该协力工作
we should
work together.
万一我们都活到最后
But what happens if we're
the last two standing?
我会毫不犹豫
I won't hesitate.
在这场比赛 杀人或被杀
This competition
is kill or be killed,
我会不考虑杀了你
and I will kill you
where you stand,
杀死了 完美的结尾
dead, end of story.
妈的不就是个人
Shit ain't personal,
买卖就是买卖 你懂吗
strictly business ya dig?
好吧 我也是这么想的
Okay. Here's what
I was thinking.
我可以生一堆火
I could set some fires
把马哥 和他的同志引到空地
to flush Marco and his crew
out into the clearing,
如果你发现弓和箭
and if you find
a bow and arrow,
你就可以解决他们
you could pick 'em off.
是的这是个伟大的想法
No, no. That's--
That's a great idea,
马哥绝对想不到
and Marco
will never see it coming.
喂
Hello?
我就在这里
I'm right here.
快跑！快跑！
Run! Run!
抓住她！
Get her!
妈的
Shit.
最后会寡不敌众
Totally outnumbered.
我该怎么办
What do I do?
仔细想想 凯迷思 仔细想想
Think, Kantmiss. Think.
痔疮的重击
Hemorrhoidal irritation.
迅速重踢他的后庭 使他痛不欲生
Aggravate with a swift
kick to the posterior.
重击！
Raah!
低晃的蛋蛋 爆破它
Low-hung scrotum.
Debilitate with
用最简单出击打球
concise rabbit punch
to the testicular sac.
矬蛋的金属牙齿矫正器
Awkward metallic orthodontic
corrective device.
抓起橡皮筋 反弹头骨
Snap rubber bands to create
blunt force to the cranium.
严重的痘痘
Rampant adolescent
acne vulgaris.
嗯
Ah.
专用外用粉刺霜膏
Prescribe
topical acne cream.
精虫充脑的宅男孩
Pubescent boy
with raging hormones.
运用天然木兰飞弹解决
Disarm with natural assets.
让你来划一下
Allow to motorboat.
你太辣了
You're pretty.
重击！
Raah!
嘻
Hee.
你准备好去死吗
You ready to die?
这不是真的！
Not really!
我的意思是 还有一线希望
I mean, kind of hoping
我能坚持撑到续集
I could stick around
for the sequel?
咦 咦
Huh?
嗯！
Mm!
好吧！ 我们知道那哨音表示什么
All right!
We know what that sound is.
中场休息
It's the end of the half.
啊 太可惜
Ah, that sucks.
我想看她被杀
I wanted
to see her die.
中场休息
Halftime
挨饿游戏 拉拉队出场
with the Starving Games
cheerleaders,
威尔刚赞助播出
presented by Viagra.
动起来 动起来
♪ Move
动起来 室内的人动起来
♪ It's time to rock the house ?
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock, rock, rock ♪
动起来 这是室内摇滚的时间
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock the house ♪
动起来 这是室内摇滚的时间
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock the house ♪
动起来 这是室内摇滚的时间
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock the house... ♪
嗯 我喜欢它 西丽 但它不是
Eh, I like it, Siri,
but it's not--
它不是激凸舞
it's not popping.
别担心 嘘 我成全你
Don't worry, boo.
I got you.
更情色 更激凸来了
More filthy and
gratuitous T&A coming up.
摇起来 摇起来
♪ Rock, rock
感受摇动 随着心情变化
♪ Feel the motion
as the mood changes ♪
圆圆  就像月亮满月
♪ Round and round
just like the moon phases ♪
继续保持 那个地方烧起来
♪ This the part that keeps
the place blazin' ♪
嗯 感觉舒畅
♪ Uh-huh
♪ Feel the vibe
我喜欢它 令人惊叹
♪ I like it, amazing
我们努力接球
♪ We go hard,
overnight ball ♪
舞会 所以它不能错过的
♪ Party right,
so it can't be wrong ♪
我的团队不会输的
♪ My team cannot lose
放开 为您表演
♪ Here to put on
a show for you ♪
动起来 动起来
♪ It's time to rock
the house ♪
动起来 这时候 晃动的房子吗
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock the house ♪
动起来 这时候 摇滚 摇滚 摇滚
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock, rock, rock ♪
动起来 这时候 晃动的房子吗
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock the house ♪
动起来 这时候 晃动的房子吗
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock the house ♪
动起来 这时候 晃动的房子吗
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock the house ♪
动起来 这时候 摇滚 摇滚
♪ Move, move
♪ It's time to rock, rock ♪
凯迷思 上半场很惊险
Kantmiss, what an
exciting first half.
请告诉我们 你现在想什么
Tell us what you're
thinking right now.
首先 我想 感谢我的主 救世主耶稣基督
First off, I want to thank my
Lord and Savior Jesus Christ.
嗯 我想 如何获胜 尸躺立
And, uh, I'm thinking
about winning, Stanley.
我只想赢得比赛
I just want to win.
鲍伯
Bob.
尸躺立你听懂了
凯迷思的意思了吗
Stanley, do you get
a sense that Kantmiss
已意识到她创造的狂热吗
is aware of the frenzy
she's creating?
我不这么认为 鲍伯
I don't think so, Bob.
她很激励人心的
She's electrifying.
砍刀中场精彩毒舌
Cleaver's Electrifying
Halftime Highlights.
啊哈！
Aah!
呀 加油
♪ Yeah
♪ Go
哦！哦！哦！ 加油
Oh! Oh! Oh!
♪ Go
看一看 什么趋势 现在推特上剖
Take a look at what's trending
right now on Twitter.
海伦在七区的呼叫
“凯迷思给我希望！”
Helen in District 7 tweets,
"Kantmiss gives me hope!"
和汤玛斯
在十一区写道
And Thomas
in District 11 writes,
“摇滚凯迷思 你辣爆了！”
"Kantmiss rocks,
UR sooooo hot!"
泰隆在康普顿区呼叫
And Tyrone in the District
of Compton tweets,
“哟 凯迷思 是一颗大炸弹”
"Yo, that ho Kantmiss
is da bomb,
她将吹起热潮！
she's mad blowin' up
in da hood, yo!"
笑脸表情符号
Smiley face emoticon.
她太红了
She is blowin' up,
并且我也有机会
and I had
the chance to be
在凯迷思专区
on the ground in
Kantmiss' own district,
其中疯凯迷思是同时间有最高人气！
where Kantmiss fever is
at an all-time high!
我现在12区
I'm here in District 12,
每个人都疯了
where everyone
is going nuts.
这是最终血拼灰姑娘的故事
It's the ultimate
underdog Cinderella story,
这里的人们就吃这一套
and the po' folks here
is eating it up,
购买任何一切有关商品指南
buying up merchandise with any
and everything that has to do
凯迷思 或挨饿的游戏有关
with Kantmiss
or the Starving Games.
T恤 马克杯
T-shirts, mugs,
手提包 杯套
totes, koozies
公仔
and bobbleheads.
看我 我就像凯迷思
Look at me.
I'm just like Kantmiss.
哦！
Ohh!
我的球
Mis cojones.
不错！直接命中！
Yes! Direct hit!
我要再射一次
I'm gonna
shoot him again.
哎！奶酪卷饼！
Ai! Cheese enchilada!
哦 那感觉很爽
Oh, that felt good.
这是一场势均力敌的 嗯
That was a close one.
Yeah.
我差一点宰了你
I almost got you.
我知道了 我当时想 “哦 ”
I know.
I was like, "Ohh."
保持先前的姿势
Take previous positions.
游戏继续！
Game on!
耶！
Yay!
你准备受死
You ready to die?
啊哈！啊哈！
Aah! Aah!
你这个小杂种！
You little turd!
嘿！
Hey!
啊哈！
Aah!
鲁迪
Rudy.
给我唱催眠曲
Sing me a lullaby.
好吧
Okay.
拉 啦啦啦
♪ La, la la la--
不是你！
Not you!
她来！
Her!
请闭上你的眼睛
♪ Please shut your eyes
你的生活是流失
♪ Your life is fading out
我要死了
Am I gonna die?
不 不 不会的
No. No, no, no.
当然 你不会死的
Of course
you're not gonna die.
是的 你会死的
♪ Yes, you are
going to die ♪
你的嘴会爬满蛆
♪ And worms
will fill your mouth ♪
蛆是不是 有点戏剧性的
Worms? Isn't that
a little dramatic?
可不可检查一下
♪ Just check right now
蛆都跑出来了
♪ The worms are all about
该死的 泰勒·斯威夫特
Damn you, Taylor Swift.
太感动了...
What an emotional and...
已隔屁了 砍刀
moving death, Cleaver.
这使我的眼球落下
It would bring
a tear to my eye
如果我的泪腺 没有撕裂
if my tear ducts
weren't lacerated.
哦 哦
Ohh.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这太扯了
This is bullshit.
中央不能对待我们像蚂蚁一样
The Capital can't just
treat us like pawns.
呀！ 呀！
Yeah!
我们的生命是我们自己的
Our life is our own,
他们不能让我们互相残杀
and they can't just
make us kill each other
为了他们病态的娱乐！
for their own
sick amusement!
呀！ 呀！
Yeah!
你们怎么说呢
What do you say?
让我们起身对抗
Let's riot
并推翻这个 极权政府
and overthrow this
totalitarian government
一劳永逸！
once and for all!
呀！ 呀！
Yeah!
喔呼！
Whoo-hoo!
我们采取半磅 A级牛肉...
We take a half-pound
of grade-A beef...
放上奶酪
and top it with cheese.
然后 我们最重要的辣椒...
Then we top it with chili...
一个热狗和排骨
and a hot dog and ribs
低热量的沙拉酱覆盖上面
and smother it with
low-cal ranch dressing.
然后我们最重要的一片 辣香肠比萨饼
Then we top it with a slice
of pepperoni pizza,
芝麻的甜面包夹上
with a sesame-seed bun.
嗯 嗯
Mmm, mmm.
嘿 呃......
Hey, uh...
我们仍然 要去对抗
are we still
gonna riot?
也许以后吧
Maybe later.
我太饿了
I'm too hungry now.
然后 我们添加 沙茶酱...
Then we add
barbeque sauce...
番茄 洋葱和生菜
tomato, onion and lettuce.
然后 我们添加了猪肉培根
Then we add pork rinds,
洋葱圈 花耶菜 玉米奶酪
Funyuns, broccoli,
nacho cheese,
罐头肉酱和鸡翅膀...
Spam and wings...
烤火腿 猪肠
and ham hocks, chitlins.
不要忘了 西瓜切片
Don't forget
the watermelon wedge.
加上两勺 开心果冰淇淋
Top it all off with two scoops
of pistachio ice cream,
并完成家最后一个芝麻面包
and finish it with
another sesame-seed bun.
600000卡路里 三层大汉堡
The 600,000 calorie
triple bypass burger.
星巴克的
Starbucks?
免费的拿铁
Got a free latte for it.
凯迷思发烧 造成 一个严重的问题
Kantmiss fever is causing
a serious problem.
我们差一点引起骚动
We almost
had a riot.
我们应该做什么呢
What should we do?
给他们更多
Give them more.
我听不懂
I don't understand.
挨饿游戏 正在火热
The Starving Games
is a hit.
只要看看报导
Just look at the trades.
我们终于可以 赢得一座艾美奖
We could finally
win an Emmy.
但节目缺少 一个重要的因素
But the show's missing
one important thing.
什么 每一个成功的表演都需要什么
What does
every successful show need
把它推到一个更新的层次
to bring it
to the next level?
我已知道 你是什么意思
I know exactly
what you mean.
一个爱情故事！
一个女同性恋的爱情故事！
A love story!
A lesbian love story!
等一下
拉拉的爱情故事
Wait.
Lesbian love story?
谁不喜欢看 两个小妞搞在一起
Who doesn't like to see
two chicks get it on?
我知道 这时候我会很喜欢的
I know I do, big time.
巴拉巴拉
♪ Guh-dunh-goh
但在这游戏其他女生
But there aren't
any other women
都隔屁了 没有其他活着
left alive
in the Games.
好吧
Fine.
那就弄个正常的爱情故事
Do your normal
straight love story.
太给他---无聊了
Bor-ing.
哦 还有 萨乐卡 ...
Oh, and, Seleca...
结束时 扔一个惊喜剧情
throw in a surprise twist
at the end,
像她死掉或某事
like she dies or something.
我喜欢这样
I like that.
巴拉 巴拉
♪ Guh-dunh-goh
注意 参赛者
Attention, contestants.
我们改变一个规则
We have a rule change.
在这游戏 现在可以有两位获胜者
There can now be two winners
of the Starving Games.
太好了 因此 马哥和彼得
Great.
So Marco and Peter
可以组队杀了我
can team up to kill me.
嗯 特别是两个人 不同的性别
Uh, specifically two people
of different genders.
哦
Oh.
好吧 不错
Okay. Okay.
所以我要去钓马哥
So I hook up with Marco,
我们一起杀了彼得
and we kill Peter together.
没错！
Yes!
嗯 我喜欢这样
Yeah. I like that.
不 我们想让你与你与彼得组队
No, we were thinking more like
you could team up with Peter.
不！ 不！
No!
不 不 我 嗯
No, no, I, um--
我喜欢跟马哥的想法更好
I like the whole
Marco idea better.
嘿 凯迷思 帮帮忙好吗
Hey, Kantmiss,
do me a favor here,
去钓彼得吧
and hook up with Peter.
Please.
不然我会没工作的
I could lose
my job for this.
现在变成我的问题了
And that's
my problem how?
哦 嘿嘿
Oh, hey.
嘿嘿 嘿 兄弟这是怎么回事呢
Heh heh. Hey, guys.
What's going on?
不 不用担心
Nah, don't worry.
它在我的控制之下 我发誓
I got it under control.
I swear.
你在--- 你在做什么
W-What are you--
What are you doing?
嗯......
Um...
哦！
Ohh!
我还以为我们是朋友
I thought
we were friends.
啊 谢谢
Ah, thanks.
我找到通往贾斯汀·比伯捷径的通行证
But I got us backstage
passes to Justin Bieber.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
不 不 你不能答应！
No. No, no,
don't you do it!
好吧
Right.
嗯 现在我要去跟彼得组队去了 所以......
Um, I'm just gonna go team up
with Peter now, so...
嗯
Hmm.
彼得 你在这里吗
Peter, are you here?
我有伪装的
I'm camouflaged.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我在这里
I'm over here.
我没有看到你
I don't see you.
我用技能变成了面包师
I used my skills
as a baker.
非常符合这种环境
to seamlessly blend in
to my surroundings.
好吧 你能不能给我一个提示吗
Okay, well,
can you give me a hint?
我在蛋糕里
I'm in the cake.
哦
Oh.
你受伤了吗
You're injured.
马哥发现我布是真心跟他
Marco found out that I
really wasn't into him
我最终是在保护你
and that I ultimately
was protecting you.
这是他做的吗
And he did this to you?
不要
No.
我给我的背部上蜡
I just got
my back waxed.
啊哈！
Aah!
哦 那 看起来不太好
Oh, that--
that looks bad.
我的意思是 这是......
I mean, it's...
哦 啊哈！
Oh.
Aah!
哦 这真的太恶心 噢 好吧
Oh, it's really oozy.
Ow. Okay.
好吧 别再戳了！
Well,
stop poking it!
好吧 我应该 好好照顾你的
Okay, well, we should
take care of you
在发病前 搞定它
before the infection
starts to take over.
来吧
Come on.
哦
Ooh.
啊哈！
Aah!
抱歉
Sorry.
请别戳了
Stop poking it, please.
好吧
Okay.
啊 他们在一起 还蛮可爱
Ah, they're cute together
是啊 好了 我还是
希望看到他们死
Yeah, well, I still
want them to die.
嗯 咄！
Yeah. Duh!
好吧
Okay.
来吧 在这里马哥不会找到我们的
Marco won't find us
in here. Come on.
我想看到他们脱光
I hope
they get naked.
来吧！
Come on!
哦
Oh.
晚上温度下降 会冻死人的
Night's falling.
It's gonna get freezing.
你发烧了
You've got a fever.
我检查我的包包
Here.
I'll check my bag
看有没有取暖的东西
for something
for warmth.
谢谢 凯迷思
Thanks, Kantmiss.
毛毯衣！
A Snuggie!
嗯 嗯
Ah. Mmm.
温暖又舒服
So warm and comfy.
什么 咦
What? Huh?
你知道...
You know...
我暗恋你很久了
I've had a crush on you
for the longest time.
每天放学 我曾经跟着你回家
I used to follow you home
from school every day.
每天
Every day.
我还记得 当你
And I remember
when you got
八岁生日拿到第一件有穿衣服的洋娃娃
your first dress-up dolly
on your eighth birthday.
而当你十二岁时
And when you turned 12
你的第一个MC来了
and got your first period.
每天晚上我看着你洗澡
I watched you shower
every night,
洗后
and after you got out,
我会在排水口收集你的头发
I would pick through the
drain and collect your hair.
什么
What?
你给我做一毛公仔呢
You made
a hair doll of me?
不只一个
Not just one.
哦
Ohh.
这是你和我
That's you and me,
而这些都是我们的六个孩子
and those are our six kids.
那是谁
And who's that?
这就是我们的小狗 阿飞
That's our puppy, Alphie.
汪汪！
Woof woof!
汪！ 恶
Woof!
Eww.
她是里面最小的
She's the runt
of the litter,
但我们爱她 都是一样的
but we love her
all the same.
哦
Ohh.
啊 你有一个毛茸茸的小妞
Ah, you got
a hairy chick, dude.
我太饿了
I'm so hungry.
可怜的宝贝
Poor baby.
这是什么 浓汤！
Soup!
What?
肯定 让你感到更好
That'll definitely
make you feel better.
嗯
Hmm?
这是什么
What?
我想他们要我们 更浪漫一些
I--I think that they want
us to be more romantic,
并且作为回报 他们会送
我们的一些东西 让你好更快
and, in return, they'll send
us stuff to make you better.
听起来不错
Sounds good to me.
对不起 戴尔
Sorry, Dale.
什么
What?!
真的吗
Really?
哦 哦 来吧
Ooh.
Oh, come on.
嘿 谁认为 他们会搞起来呢
Hey, who thinks
they're gonna do it?
我们要看！ 我们要看！
We do!
太贼了你们！
Screw you all!
现在要干吗(纸条:快表演精彩的)
What is it now?
这是对的！
All right!
彼得 我不知道我能不能做到这一点
Peter, I don't know
if I can do this.
哦 我的背部
Oh, my back.
我快要死了
I'm dying.
我不知道我能坚持下去多久
I don't know how much
longer I can hang on.
好的 让我们...
All right. Let's...
给他们想要的
give them
what they want.
太棒了
Fantastic.
同感
True dat.
噢 嗷！
Ow. Ow!
你不能用力捏我的屁股
Can you not grab
my butt so hard?
我没有捏你的屁股
I'm not touching
your butt at all.
哦！
Ohh!
不要害怕
Do not be afraid.
我只是 一位慈祥的老巫师
I am but
a kindly old wizard.
把手移开我的屁股！
Get your hand
off my ass!
好吧 嗯......
Right. Well...
让我解释一下
let me explain.
你看 我们正在旅行
You see,
we were traveling.
我们
We were on--
我们要去的方向
We were on our way
迷雾
to the Misty--
迷雾山 是的
the Misty
Mountains, yes.
我们听到了呻吟声
And then
we heard a moan
来自 这个洞穴里面
coming from
inside this cave,
担心这是惨叫的呻吟
and fearing it to be
a moan of distress
做为好心的矮人
and being the good
Samaritans that we are,
我们来到这里 帮助你
we came in here
to help you.
滚出去！
Get out!
是的 好的 好的
Yes. Well. Okay.
哪掰掰了
I bid you adieu.
哦 哦
Ooh.
哦 宝贝
♪ Ooh, baby
你知道吗 我们怎么办
♪ You know what
we're gonna do ♪
这是做爱的时间
♪ It's time
for makin' love ♪
哇！
Whoa!
只有我和你
♪ Just me and you
♪ Just me and you ♪
哦 宝贝
♪ Oh, baby
你知道 我们来到了什么办
♪ You know
what we came to do ♪
喔 凯迷思
这是做爱的时间
Aww. Kantmiss.
♪ It's time for makin' love
只有我和你 喜欢吗
♪ Just me and you
Like that♪
是啊 爱它！
我喜欢它！呀！
Yeah, love it!
I love it! Yeah!
不是她的第一次吧
Not her first trip
to the rodeo, eh?
哦 耶！哦 凯迷思！
Oh, yeah! Oh, Kantmiss!
呀！哦！
Yeah! Oh!
哇！ 哇
Wow!
Whoa.
哦！ 哦！
Ohh!
噢 彼得 太好了！
Oh, Peter, yes!
厉害！
Score!
甚至我都没办法做这招！
Even I don't get
to do that!
哦 给我你的手 哦 天啊
Oh, give me your hand.
Oh, God.
没错！
Yes!
老汉推车 没错！
Ride the donkey. Yes!
哦！哦！
Ohh! Ohh!
看3D更爽
And it's
even better in 3-D.
因为现在你在这里
♪ 'Cause now
that you're here ♪
我就要去了...
♪ I'm gonna...
哦 哦
Ooh.
哦 宝贝 呀
♪ Oh, baby
♪ Yeah
十二区！
你知道我们要做什么
District 12!
♪ You know what we're gonna do
这就是它！
这是做爱的时间
That's it!
♪ It's time for makin' love
哦 哦
Ooh.
只有我和你
啊
♪ Just me and you
Ahh.
哇哦 哇
♪ Whoa, oh, whoa
昨晚 再次感谢
Thanks again
for last night.
现在你好多了
Now that you're better,
我们必须出发
we have to go out there.
我们必须杀了马哥
我们就可以双赢和回家
We have to kill Marco so we can
both win the game and go home.
我 我会的 但...
I--I would, but...
我认为又发病了
I think the infection's
starting to come back.
不要摸它！
Don't push it!
你想要去哪里
Where do you think
you're going?
你不能进去！
You can't go in there!
哇！你---哈！
Whoa! Did you--Ha!
他在那里的
He's right there.
他们什么时候会互相残杀吗
When are they gonna
kill each other already?
我觉得越来越无聊
我也一样
I'm getting bored.
Me, too.
啊哈！
Aah!
是该结束了
一劳永逸了
It's time to end this
once and for all.
西丽
Siri.
当！ 你现在需要什么
Dang!
What you need now?
给我们压轴
Let's have a grand finale.
送上大枪
Send in the big guns.
哦 屎蛋
Oh, shit.
我会给你一个想像不到的战争
I'll give you a war
you wouldn't believe.
后会有期 宝贝
Hasta la vista, baby.
我一定会回来的
Yippie-ki-yay--
哦
Oh.
该死的 我都没有一句名言
Damn it. I don't
have a catchphrase.
哈哈哈！ 我有很多
Ha ha ha!
I have so many of them.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
你知道我的意思吧 查克
You know what
I mean, Chuck?
不知
No.
因为我 查克·诺里斯
Because I'm
Chuck Norris,
名言需要我！
and catchphrases need me!
嗯
Enh.
你们为什么不闭嘴
Why don't you shut up,
你们一群自以为聪明的狗屎
you smarty-pants wisenheimer
piece of shit?!
让我们杀了他们
Let's just kill 'em.
哦
Oh.
准备好了！
Ready!
瞄准
Aim.
好的！
Yes!
哟 安德烈！
Yo, Adrian!
开火！
Fire!
巴拉 巴拉！
Gah!
戴尔
Dale?
你这家伙 这是怎么回事呢
What's going on
with you and this guy?
我待会再告诉你
I'll talk to you
about it later.
我看到你亲他
I saw you kiss him.
我在死亡比赛中
I am in the middle
of a death match.
你喜欢他吗
Do you like him?
戴尔 你让我很尴尬
Dale, you are
embarrassing me.
回家
喏
Go home.
Nyah.
不！如果有人应该离开...
No! If anyone should leave...
应该是他
he should.
好吧 嗯
我 我离开
Okay. Yeah.
I-I'll leave.
现在 戴尔！
好吧
Now, Dale!
Fine.
好吧！
Fine!
现在我要把我的脸书改成单身
But I'm changing my
Facebook status to single.
我们对此深感抱歉
Sorry about that.
他总是黏巴达
He's always
been really clingy.
这很酷的
That's cool.
令人难以置信
Unbelievable.
你现在要怎么办 凯迷思
What are you
gonna do, Kantmiss?
你射歪 情人小狼狗就会隔屁
You shoot and miss,
lover boy here is dead.
没错！
Yes!
不 不 不 不！
No, no, no, no!
咦 咦
Huh?
耶
Yeah.
哦！ 哦！
Oh!
这真的有用
That'll work.
怎么样 砍刀
How about that, Cleaver?
排除万难他们已经做到了 他们已经赢了
Against all odds,
they've done it. They've won.
耶
Yay.
呼！
Whew!
彼得 我们赢了
Peter, we won.
我们活下来了！
We survived!
我们要回家了
We're both going home.
注意 参赛者
Attention, contestants.
规则又有改变
There has been
yet another rule change.
如果你想 我在想什么
And if you're thinking
what I'm thinking,
你猜对了
you're right.
规则又改回 只能有一个胜利者
There again
can be only one winner.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
如果 我们不让他们称心如意呢
What if we don't give
'em the satisfaction?
如果我们都自杀
What if we
both kill ourselves
就没有胜利者
and there
are no victors?
我们就毁了游戏
We'll ruin the Games,
我们会告诉中央
and we'll show
th-that the Capital,
他们无法控制我们！
they can't control us!
在树林中我发现这些 有毒的果实
I found these poisonous
berries in the woods.
我们可以吃了一起死
W-We can eat them
a-and die.
妈的这不个人问题
Shit ain't personal,
买卖归买卖 你了解吗
strictly business,
ya dig?
哇！呼！
Whaah! Whoa!
我操！
Fuck me!
挨饿游戏永垂不朽！
Best Starving Games ever!
那一箭射得真好 凯迷思
It's a nice shot,
Kantmiss.
你们是干什么 在这里干么
What're you
doing here?
我几乎露脸
I practically show up
在每部电影结束时
at the end
of every movie.
超级英雄电影 没错 但
Superhero movies,
yeah, but--
嗯 这是我想要和你谈谈的
Well, that's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
我们可以使用 一些新鲜年轻的生力军
We could use
some fresh, young blood.
我的意思是 该死！
I mean, shit!
究竟有多少续集 “钢铁人”
Just how many sequels
to "Iron Man,"
“雷神”和“美国队长” 我们可以做 对不对
"Thor" and "Captain America"
can we make, right?
你弓箭玩的不错
And you're pretty handy
with that bow and arrow.
咳咳！
Ahem!
嗯 尼克 嗯
Uh, Nick, the, uh,
弓和箭 是我的专业
bow and arrow
is sort of my thing.
闭上你的屁眼 鹰眼！
Shut your ass, Hawkeye!
你能在复仇者联盟 你就很幸运！
You're lucky you
even in the Avengers!
但是 而且你不觉得
Yeah, but--
And don't you think
就是一分钟
for one goddamn minute
电影公司 也会把你这人物给删了！
that Marvel is gonna
spin off your character!
“鹰眼” 结肠癌 隔了
"Hawkeye, colon,
“复仇者联盟 ”不会关心一堆狗屎的
The Avenger Nobody
Gives a Shit About,"
肯定不会受你不出现的威胁！
will definitely not be coming
soon to a theater near you!
燃烧吧！
Burn!
烧录
Burn.
哦
Ow.
别叽叽歪歪了！
Oh, stop being
such a cherry!
所以你认为怎样 凯迷思
So what do you say,
Kantmiss?
我加入
I'm in.
但是 嗯 我有点饿了
But, um,
I'm kind of hungry.
你不介意 我们先去找吃的东西吗
Do you mind if we get
something to eat first?
让我们去弄一些 沙威玛烤肉
Let's go get
some shawarma.
复仇者联盟集合！
Avengers assemble!
等一下 不要踩到那些机关
Wait, don't step
off those--
哎呀
Oops.
哦！你知道吗 那声音意味着什么
Oh! You know
what that sound means?
鲍伯的片后NG片段
Bob's Post-Game Bloopers.
动起来
♪ Move
啊哈！ 哇 哇 哇
Aah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
动起来...
♪ Move...
好
Good.
搞笑片段
Blooper reel.
动起来 室内的人动起来
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock the house ♪
室内的人动起来...
♪ It's time
to rock the house... ♪
哦
Ohh.
抱歉
Sorry.
室内的人动起来 动起来...
♪ It's time to rock the house ♪
♪ Move...
搞笑片段！
Blooper reel!
切！ 呀！
Cutting!
Yeah!
动起来 室内的人动起来...
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock the house... ♪
哦
Oh.
假发要掉了
And the wig is down.
好吧 对不起
Okay. I'm sorry.
我得比你更兴奋
I gotta get
more excited about you.
让我们开始
Let's do it.
摸我的大腿
Touch my leg.
好了 我们走吧
Here we go.
戴尔 别来
Dude, stop.
恶作剧 来一个
Prank, take one.
哦！
Ohh!
看看你！
Look at you!
戴尔 这真是浪漫
Dale, that's
romantic and all.
是的 你为什么不跳一下舞吗
Yes, why don't you
give me a little dance?
蹦恰恰 蹦恰恰
♪ Boom, chika, boom, chika ♪
没跟上节拍
♪ Boom, chika, boom,
boom, chika be ♪
再来一次
On the down, not the up.
蹦 恰 蹦 恰
♪ Be, chika, boom chik
很好 现在看起来像一只企鹅
That's good.
Now like a penguin.
蹦 恰 蹦 恰
♪ Boom, chika,
boom, chika ♪
蹦 恰 蹦 恰
♪ Boom, chika, boo--
这是我见过最糟糕的企鹅 再来一次
That's the worst penguin I've ever seen.
Do it again.
蹦 恰 蹦 恰
♪ Boom, chika,
boom, chika ♪
你喜欢看矮人吗
Do you like
watching Pygmies?
哦 是的 哦 这看起来不错
Oh, yeah. Oh.
That looks good.
看看汗留下来
Look at that dripping.
我刚在我的背部上蜡
I just got
my back waxed.
对不起
I'm sorry.
踢 哈！
Kick.
Hah!
抱歉
Sorry.
我踢到你的屁股
I kicked your ass.
不 没关系 没事......
No, that's fine.
Don't...
室内的人动起来...
♪ It's time
to rock the house... ♪
这 是我的好火鸡
And this
is my sidekick.
姥姥不爱 我刚刚说了什么
Mother pus.
What'd I say?
和我
With me.
这是...
And this is...
嘘 我的好火鸡
Shh.
...my sidekick.
这是我的好火鸡
And this is my sidekick.
嗯 那很滑稽 你脸上有一条线
Yeah. That's funny.
You got one line.
你开始
You do.
准备好了吗
Ready?
而且我有另一个台词 踢死
And I have
another Tess Tickles.
我需要看到一个双向的台词 踢死
I need to see a bi--
不 它不是 “我要看的 ”
No, it's not,
"I need to see."
别隐藏了出来吧
Stop hiding, and show me--
他妈的
God damn it.
我需要一对的台词 踢死！
I need a pair
of Tess Tickles!
妈的
Shit.
捕蚊器
For bug zapper.
摸一摸
Contact.
摸一摸 摸一摸
Contact. Contact.
噢噢
Uh-oh.
等一下
Hold on.
室内的人动起来
♪ It's time to rock
the house ♪
动起来 现在是摇滚时间 摇滚 摇滚
♪ Move
♪ It's time to rock, rock, rock ♪
动起来 室内的人动起来
? Move
♪ It's time to rock the house ♪
动起来 室内的人动起来
♪ Move
? It's time to rock the house ♪
对不起
I'm sorry.
动起来 现在是摇滚时间...
♪ Move
? It's time to rock, rock, rock... ♪
吃了一部分的酸黄瓜
A partially eaten pickle.
挨饿游戏 玩的快乐
So happy Starving Games,
也祝你们好运
and may the odds
be never in your favor.
这是我吃过最烂的酸黄瓜
That is the worst pickle
I've ever had.
我们必须杀马哥 并赢得比赛
We have to kill Marco
and win the games.
抱歉 啊 抱歉
Sorry. Ahh. Sorry.
我们必须杀马哥 然后我们可以回家
We have to kill Marco
so we can both go home
赢得比 他妈的 抱歉
and win the ga--
God damn it. Sorry.
动起来
♪ Move
现在是摇滚时间 摇滚 摇滚...
♪ It's time to rock, rock, rock... ♪
动起来
♪ Move
哇 太不可思议
Wow, that's amazing.
吃起来不错 那是什么
That is good.
What is that?
这是一个神圣的混合物
It's a divine mixture
狐狸和熊的血
of fox blood
and bear
很好吃吧 对吗
Delicious. Right?
嘿！
Hey!
嘿，菲尔，待在那里
Hey, Phil, stay down there
把你的手指头
放到他的嘴里去
and put your finger
in his mouth.
好吧 我们就大功告成了
Okay. We're done.
就玩到这里
We're done with this.
搞笑片段
Blooper reel.
停！
Cutting!
动起来
♪ Move
动起来 动起来 动起来
♪ Move, move, move
动起来
♪ Move